https://www.softdb.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy | Soft dB
Sound MaskingConsultingInstruments
1-866-686-0993
LanguagesFrançaisEspañolEnglish
SOUND MASKINGWhat is Sound Masking?Who Needs Sound Masking?How Much Does It Cost?System FeaturesProven BenefitsEquipment & SoftwareDocumentationContact & DistributorsOur ClientsACOUSTICAL CONSULTINGMonitoring SolutionsSoundproofing SolutionsEnvironmental AcousticsIndustrial AcousticsArchitectural AcousticsVibration ControlAeroacousticsAcoustical ImageryOur Consulting OfficesOur ClientsINSTRUMENTSNoise Measuring ToolsNoise Analysis SoftwareNoise Mapping SystemDigital Signal ProcessingScanning Probe MicroscopyBlogNewsEventsCareersSOUND MASKINGWhat is Sound Masking?Who Needs Sound Masking?How Much Does It Cost?System FeaturesProven BenefitsEquipment & SoftwareDocumentationContact & DistributorsOur ClientsACOUSTICAL CONSULTINGMonitoring SolutionsSoundproofing SolutionsEnvironmental AcousticsIndustrial AcousticsArchitectural AcousticsVibration ControlAeroacousticsAcoustical ImageryOur Consulting OfficesOur ClientsINSTRUMENTSNoise Measuring ToolsNoise Analysis SoftwareNoise Mapping SystemDigital Signal ProcessingScanning Probe MicroscopyBlogNewsEventsCareersPrivacy PolicySoft dB strives to ensure the protection of your personal information through responsible practices.We deploy all efforts to protect the private nature of your personal information. Since we collect information about you using our website, we feel that it is important that you understand how we collect and use this information. This page summarizes our personal information collection practices.Personal information collectionAll personal information collected by Soft dB is done so exclusively with your consent, by means of a form posted on our website, an email received from you or by telephone. No information is collected automatically.Use of your personal informationThe personal information collected is only used by Soft dB staff for the purposes defined at the time of the collection or a use that complies with these purposes. We do not share your information with any third parties.As mentioned above, we use your personal information to appropriately process your requests and present you with the information you need to access. We also use all of the information you provide voluntarily in order to make your visits on our site possible. This information might, at a later time, allow us to add customized elements to our site or to plan its content more appropriately, based on user interests.If you have granted us the permission to, we can use your personal information in order to send you newsletters, with the intent of offering you the best service possible.At all times, the sender of any email received from Soft dB is easily identifiable and reachable, via email or phone.Sharing of your personal informationWe will not, under any circumstances, share your personal information with other individuals or organizations without your permission, including public organizations, corporations or individuals, except when applicable by law. We do not sell, communicate or divulge your information to any mailing lists. We do not share your personal information with any of our business partners, including our CEU course hosters who collect their own information, whenever applicable (e.g. when you register as attendee to one of our CEU events), but always with your full prior consent.The only exception is if the law or a court order compels us to. We will share your information with government agencies if they need or request it.Use of cookiesWe use a component of your browser named a cookie to recognize your computer. Cookies are small data files that are saved on your hard drive when you visit websites. These files make browsing the sites easier.We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve your personal information from your computer. The information collected is instead used for statistical purposes, among others to compute the number of visitors and find out which pages are the most visited.If you configure your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, a prompt will pop-up each time a site asks for permission to save a cookie on your computer. You can refuse cookies by configuring your browser to reject them.Storage and safety of your personal informationWe store your file ourselves. In addition, we use and apply the appropriate security measures to preserve the confidentiality of your information.Soft dB notably uses software to monitor traffic on its network in order to detect unauthorized attempts to download or change information, or to otherwise damage the site. This software receives and records the IP address of the computer used by the person visiting our website, the date and time of the visit and the pages viewed. We do not attempt to make the connection between these addresses and the identities of the individuals who visit our site, unless an intrusion or disruption attempt is detected.Legal protectionAll personal information you supply Soft dB is protected according to the federal government’s Privacy Act. This means that you are entitled to know when the information is collected and to be informed of the purpose of such collection, but also to access said information. We are legally bound to save all personal information you provide for at least two years after their use so that you may reasonably access them. After that time, your personal information will be destroyed.Access to and viewing of your personal informationYou can, at any time, access the personal information we have collected about you, modify it or ask us to delete it. To do so, or if you have any questions or comments regarding this policy, please contact us.Limits of our policyOur website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.Changes to this policyAt our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect current acceptable practices. We will take reasonable steps to let users know about changes via our website. Your continued use of this site after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information.If we make a significant change to this privacy policy, for example changing a lawful basis on which we process your personal information, we will ask you to re-consent to the amended privacy policy.Soft dB Data Controller
info@softdb.comSoft dB Data Protection Officer
info@softdb.comThis policy is effective as of 13 March 2019.Soft dBAcoustics & Vibration Experts
Head Office
1040 Belvedere Ave. #215, Quebec QC G1S 3G3
1-866-686-0993 (USA & Canada)
1-418-686-0993 (Intl.)
Montreal Office
250 Dunbar Ave. #203, Mont-Royal QC H3P 2H5
1-877-774-3800 (USA & Canada)
1-514-727-3800 (Intl.)
Stay Informed With Our Newsletter
Subscribe
Sound MaskingHow It WorksWho Needs ItOur ClientsSystem FeaturesKey BenefitsEquipmentSpecs & ManualsDistributorsConsultingArchitecturalEnvironmentalIndustrialAeroacousticsAcoustical ImagerySoundproofingVibration ControlContactInstrumentsNoise MeasurementNoise MappingRemote MonitoringDSP BoardsMicroscopyResourcesBlogLatest NewsEventsDocumentationAcoustics GlossaryROI CalculatorContinuing Education
Copyright All Rights Reserved - Soft dB © 2020Privacy PolicyUse of CookiesTerms of ServiceSitemap
By continuing to use the site you agree to our
privacy policy. I agree
